helpmedoc.in 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy

1\. Introduction  
LaZoi formerly known as HelpMeDoc (“us,” “we,” or “LaZoi”) is committed to respecting the privacy rights of our customers, visitors, and other users of HelpMeDoc.in (the “Site”) and related websites, applications, services and mobile applications provided by LaZoi and on/in which this Privacy Policy is posted or referenced (collectively, the “Services”). We created this Privacy Policy (“Privacy Policy”) to give you confidence as you use the Services and to demonstrate our commitment to the protection of privacy. This Privacy Policy is only applicable to the Services. This Privacy Policy does not apply to any other website or digital service that you may be able to access through the Services or any website or digital services of LaZoi’s business partners, each of which may have data collection, storage and use practices and policies that may materially differ from this Privacy Policy. Your use of the Services is governed by this Privacy Policy and the Agreement (as the term “Agreement” is defined in our Terms of Use). Any capitalized term used but not defined in this Privacy Policy shall have the meaning in the Agreement.

BY USING THE SERVICES, YOU AGREE TO THE PRACTICES AND POLICIES OUTLINED IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND YOU HEREBY CONSENT TO THE COLLECTION, USE, AND SHARING OF YOUR INFORMATION AS DESCRIBED IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH THIS PRIVACY POLICY, YOU CANNOT USE THE SERVICES. IF YOU USE THE SERVICES ON BEHALF OF SOMEONE ELSE (SUCH AS YOUR CHILD) OR AN ENTITY (SUCH AS YOUR EMPLOYER), YOU REPRESENT THAT YOU ARE AUTHORIZED BY SUCH INDIVIDUAL OR ENTITY TO ACCEPT THIS PRIVACY POLICY ON SUCH INDIVIDUAL'S OR ENTITY'S BEHALF.

2\. Information we collect:

2.1 Personal Information  
2.1.1 Personal Information Generally

Some of the Services require us to know more about you so that we can best meet your needs. When you access these Services, we may ask you to voluntarily provide us certain information that personally identifies (or could be used to personally identify) you (“Personal Information”). Personal Information includes (but is not limited to) the following categories of information: (1) contact data (such as your e-mail address and phone number) (2) demographic data (such as your gender, your date of birth and your zip code) (3) insurance data (such as your insurance carrier, insurance plan, member ID, group ID and payer ID) (4) medical data (such as the doctors, dentists or other health care providers (“Healthcare Providers”) you have visited, your reasons for visit, your dates of visit, your medical history, and other medical and health information you choose to share with us), and (5) other information that you voluntarily choose to provide to us, including without limitation SSN, unique identifiers such as passwords, and Personal Information in emails or letters that you send to us. You may still access and use some of the Services if you choose not to provide us with any Personal Information, but the features of the Services that require your Personal Information will not be accessible to you.

2.1.2 Billing, Collection and Payment Information  
When you make a payment through our Services to a Healthcare Provider (as further described in and subject to other provisions of the Agreement), your payment card information is processed by our payment processing partner, CCAvenue(https://CCavenue.com). CCavenue collects your voluntarily provided payment card information necessary to process your payment. CCavenue’s use and storage of information it collects is governed by Stripe’s applicable terms of service and privacy policy. The information we store includes your payment card type and the last four digits of the payment card. We may provide to you the option to remove your stored payment card information through your account settings page.

2.2 Traffic Data  
We also may automatically collect certain data when you use the Services, such as (1) IP address (2) domain server (3) type of device(s) used to access the Services (4) web browser(s) used to access the Services (5) referring webpage or other source through which you accessed the Services (6) geolocation information and (7) other statistics and information associated with the interaction between your browser or device and the Services (collectively “Traffic Data”). Depending on applicable law, some Traffic Data may be Personal Information.

We may also collect additional information, which may be Personal Information, as otherwise described to you at the point of collection or pursuant to your consent.

3\. Public Information  
Any information that you may reveal in a review posting or online discussion or forum is intentionally open to the public and is not in any way private. We recommend that you carefully consider whether to disclose any Personal Information in any public posting or forum. What you have written may be seen and/or collected by third parties and may be used by others in ways we are unable to control or predict.

4\. . Storage and Security of Information  
The security of your Personal Information is important to us. We endeavor to follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the Personal Information submitted to us, both during transmission and in storage. For example, when you enter sensitive information on our Site, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology.

Although we make good faith efforts to store Personal Information in a secure operating environment that is not open to the public, we do not and cannot guarantee the security of your Personal Information. If we become aware that your Personal Information has been disclosed in a manner not in accordance with this Privacy Policy, we will use reasonable efforts to notify you of the nature and extent of the disclosure (to the extent we know that information) as soon as reasonably possible and as permitted or required by law.

5\. Cancellation and Refund Policy  
While LaZoi will try to ensure a confirmed appointment for a End-User who requested an appointment on Website, LaZoi does not guarantee that a patient will get a confirmed appointment. Further, LaZoi has no liability if such appointment is confirmed by the practioner but later cancelled by the Practitioners for some reason, or the Practitioners are not available as per the given appointment time.

Miscellaneous:

1.By using the present application software, you acknowledge and agree that LaZoi may access, preserve, and disclose your information and any content associated with your account if required to do so by law or in a good faith belief that such access preservation or disclosure is reasonably necessary to:  
1.Satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request  
2.Enforce the terms, including investigation of potential violations hereof  
3.Detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues (including, without limitation, the filtering of spam) or  
4.Protect against imminent harm to the rights, property or safety of LaZoi, its users or the public as required or permitted by law.  
LaZoi is committed to protecting your privacy. Security measures for this site and protection of your data have been taken to protect against loss, misuse or alteration of the information you provide and industry standard encryption methods are used to assure security. Nevertheless, it is crucial that, as a user, you protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer and that you always sign off when finished using a shared computer. Further, you should be aware that no system is impenetrable. Thus, it is your responsibility to diligently monitor your credit card statements, bank statements and similar personal information so as to discover and address as quickly as possible any misuse of your personal information."
